Genetics Society of America Records 1921-1982 Mss.575.06.G28p
American Philosophical Society
- Genetics Society of America Records, 1921-1984; 24.5 Linear feet 24.5 lin. feet
  - Records, 1968 (Box 26)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1968; 27 folders (Box 26)
      - Boards, Committees and Representatives, 1968 (Box 26)
      - Committee on Maintenance of Genetic Stocks, 1968 (Box 26)
      - Committees, 1968 (Box 26)
      - Concerning Secret Commitments, 1968 (Box 26)
      - Cornell University, 1968 (Box 26)
      - Information Requests, 1968 (Box 26)
      - Mailing List, 1968 (Box 26)
      - Membership Records, 1968; 4 folders (Box 26)
      - Nominating Committee, 1968 (Box 26)
      - Obituaries, 1968 (Box 27)
      - Records, 1968; 4 folders (Box 27)
      - Representatives, 1968; 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Sustaining Members, 1968 (Box 27)
      - Treasurer's Records, 1968; 2 folders (Box 27)
    - International Congress - Travel Complaints, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Irwin, M R, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Lewis, E B, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Love, Askell, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Mosig, Gisela, 1968 (Box 27)
    - National Science Foundation, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Professional Associates, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Roman, Herschel, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Stadler, David R, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Wagner, R P, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Yanofsky, Charles, 1968 (Box 27)
  - Records, 1969 (Box 27)
    - Agricultural Research Institution, 1969 (Box 27)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1969; 2 folders (Box 27)
    - American Type Culture Collection - Representative, 1969 (Box 27)
    - Ash, William J, 1969 (Box 27)
    - Fabergé, A C, 1969 (Box 27)
    - Genetics, 1969; 3 folders (Box 27)
    - Giles, Norman H, 1969 (Box 27)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1969; 23 folders (Box 27)
      - Agenda, 1969 (Box 27)
      - Annual Meeting, 1969; 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Annual Meeting - Minutes, 1969 (Box 27)
      - Annual Meeting - Program, 1969; 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Annual Report, 1969 (Box 27)
      - Board of Directors, 1969 (Box 27)
      - Call for Papers, 1969 (Box 27)
      - Committees, 1969; 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Constitution, 1969 (Box 27)
      - Education Committee, 1969 (Box 27)
      - Election Results, 1969 (Box 27)
      - Membership Records, 1969; 4 folders (Box 27)
      - Nominating Committee, 1969 (Box 27)
      - Obituaries, 1969 (Box 28)
      - Representatives, 1969 (Box 28)
      - Sustaining Members, 1969 (Box 28)
      - Treasurer's Records, 1969 (Box 28)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1969 (Box 28)
    - Professional Associates, 1969 (Box 28)
    - Roman, Herschel, 1969 (Box 28)
    - Snyder, L A, 1969 (Box 28)
    - Topalow, Michael, 1969 (Box 28)
    - Townsend, J Ives, 1969 (Box 28)
    - Yanofsky, Charles, 1969; 7 folders (Box 28)
  - Records, 1970 (Box 28)
    - Allard, R W, 1970 (Box 28)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1970 (Box 28)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1970; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - American Society for Cell Biology, 1970 (Box 28)
    - American Society of Agronomy, 1970 (Box 28)
    - American Society of Biological Chemists, 1970 (Box 28)
    - American Type Culture Collection, 1970 (Box 28)
    - Cleland, Ralph E, 1970 (Box 28)
    - De Serres, Frederick J, 1970 (Box 28)
    - First National Biological Congress, 1970 (Box 28)
    - Genetics, 1970; 9 folders (Box 28)
      - Genetics, 1970; 4 folders (Box 28)
      - Financial Correspondence, 1970; 3 folders (Box 28)
      - Financial Records, 1970 (Box 28)
      - General Correspondence, 1970 (Box 28)
    - Giles, Norman H, 1970; 3 folders (Box 28)
    - Goldschmidt, Josef, 1970 (Box 28)
      re. Elizabeth
    - Genetics Society of America, 1970; 26 folders (Box 28)
      - Abstracts, 1970 (Box 28)
      - Annual Meeting, 1970 (Box 28)
      - Auditor's Report, 1970 (Box 28)
      - Board of Directors, 1970 (Box 28)
      - Board of Directors - Minutes, 1970 (Box 28)
      - Boards, Committee and Representatives, 1970 (Box 28)
      - Committee on Education, 1970 (Box 28)
      - Committee on Honors & Awards, 1970 (Box 28)
      - Committee on Maintenance of Genetic Stocks, 1970 (Box 28)
      - Committee on Public Relations, 1970 (Box 28)
      - Elections, 1970 (Box 28)
      - Membership Records, 1970; 6 folders (Box 29)
      - Nominating Committee, 1970 (Box 29)
      - Obituaries, 1970 (Box 29)
      - Secretary's Report, 1970 (Box 29)
      - Sustaining Members, 1970 (Box 29)
      - Sustaining Membership Committee, 1970 (Box 29)
      - Treasurer's Records, 1970; 4 folders (Box 29)
    - Hanks, George D, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Hartwell, Leland, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Hays, Florence C, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Hutt, F B, 1970 (Box 29)
    - International Genetics Federation, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Lederberg, Joshua, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Lerner, Michael et. al., 1970 (Box 29)
    - Lewis, E G, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Lindsley, Dan L, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Myers, W M, 1970 (Box 29)
    - National Council on Radiation Protection & Measurements, 1970 (Box 29)
    - National Research Council, 1970 (Box 29)
    - National Research Council - Agricultural Board, 1970 (Box 29)
    - National Science Foundation, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Polivanov, Sergey, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Ravin, Arnold W, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Roman, Herschel L, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Senker, Thomas J, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Shaw, Margery W, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Stadler, David R, 1970; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Strauss, Bernard S, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Stelly, Matthias, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Strömnaes, Oistein, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Thirteenth International Congress of Genetics - Minutes of National Committee, 1970 (Box 29)
    - University of Calif., Berkeley - Department of Genetics - Anti-War Campaign, 1970 (Box 29)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Vickery, Robert K Jr., 1970 (Box 29)
    - Wagner, Robert P, 1970 (Box 29)
      - * American Society for Cell Biology, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Wallace, Bruce, 1970 (Box 29)
  - Records, 1971 (Box 29)
    - American Association for Advancement of Scienc, 1971 (Box 29)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences, 1971 (Box 29)
    - American Society of Agronomy, 1971 (Box 29)
    - American Society of Biological Chemists, 1971 (Box 29)
    - American Type Culture Collection, 1971 (Box 29)
    - Anderson, V Elving, 1971 (Box 29)
    - Baker, William K, 1971 (Box 29)
    - Berg, Claire M, 1971 (Box 29)
    - Black, C A, 1971 (Box 29)
    - California - Sec. of State, 1971 (Box 29)
    - Committee on American Council for Agricultural Science, 1971 (Box 29)
    - de Serres, Frederick J, 1971 (Box 29)
    - Environmental Directory for Agricultural Science, 1971 (Box 29)
    - Forro, Frederick, Jr., 1971 (Box 29)
    - Genetical Society (Gt. Britain), 1971 (Box 30)
    - Genetics, 1971; 3 folders (Box 30)
      - Genetics, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Financial Records, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Records, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Genetics Society of Canada, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Giles, Norman H, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Griffing, Bruce, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Annual Meeting, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Annual Meeting - Registrants, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Auditor's Report, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Board of Directors, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Committee for Liaison with Sister Societies, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Committee on Honors and Awards, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Committee on Maintenance of Genetic Stocks, 1971; 2 folders (Box 30)
      - Committee on Public Relations, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Committee on State of the Society & Journal, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Finance Committee, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Genetics Training Committee, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Membership Records, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Newsletters, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Nominating Committee, 1971 (Box 30)
      - Sustaining Membership Committee, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Hartman, Philip E, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Hotchkiss, Rolin D, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Institute of Scientific Information, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Lefevre, George Jr., 1971 (Box 30)
    - Lewis, Herman, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Lewontin, R C, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Moorhead, Paul S, 1971 (Box 30)
    - National Council on Radiation Protection, 1971 (Box 30)
    - National Research Council, 1971 (Box 30)
    - National Research Council - Division of Biology & Agriculture, 1971 (Box 30)
    - National Science Foundation, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Second International Biological Congress, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Spiess, Eliot B, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Stadler, David, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Stadler Genetics Symposium, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Snustad, Peter, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Wagner, Robert P, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Wallace, Bruce, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Woodward, V W, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Yanofsky, Charles, 1971 (Box 30)
  - Records, 1972 (Box 30)
    - Black, C A, 1972 (Box 30)
    - Brazilian Society for Advancement of Science, 1972 (Box 30)
    - Caspari, Ernst, 1972 (Box 30)
    - Genetics, 1972 (Box 30)
    - Genetics Society of Chile, 1972 (Box 30)
    - Genetics Society of America, 1972 (Box 30)
      - Membership Records, 1972; 9 folders (Box 30)
    - Hobbs, Dane, 1972 (Box 30)
    - Lefevre, George Jr., 1972 (Box 30)
    - National Council on Radiation Protection, 1972 (Box 30)
    - National Institutes of Health - Division of Research Services, 1972 (Box 30)
    - Snustad, Peter, 1972 (Box 30)
    - Wagner, Robert P, 1972 (Box 30)
  - Records, 1973 (Box 31)
    - XIII International Congress of Genetics, 1973; Approximately 200 folders
      Committee activities; Conferences and symposia; Genetics Society of America; International Congress of Genetics -- Thirteenth Congress; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics, 1973; 5 folders (Box 31)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Abstracts, 1973; 6 folders (Box 31)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Finance Committee, 1973; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Finance Committee - Correspondence, 1973; 5 folders (Box 31)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Finance Committee - Correspondence - National Institute of Health, 1973; 4 folders (Box 31)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Finance Committee - Correspondence - National Science Foundation, 1973; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Finance Committee - Financial Aid - Brazil, 1973 (Box 31)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Finance Committee - Grant Proposal, 1973; 2 folders (Box 31)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Finance Committee - Travel Awards, 1973; 4 folders (Box 31)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Financial Statements - Correspondence, 1973; 3 folders (Box 31)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Financial Statements - Disbursements, 1973; 5 folders (Box 31)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Financial Statements - Disbursements, 1973; 2 folders (Box 32)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Financial Statements - Income Tax, 1973 (Box 32)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Foreign Correspondence (A-Z), 1973; 23 folders (Box 32)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - General Correspondence, 1973; 4 folders (Box 32)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Grant Applications, 1973; 2 folders (Box 32)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Grants, 1973 (Box 32)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Invitations, 1973; 3 folders (Box 32)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Invitations, 1973; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Local Organizing Committee, 1973 (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Miscellaneous - Thank you letters, 1973 (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Miscellaneous - Entertainment/Tours, 1973 (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1973; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - National Organizing Committee, 1973; 3 folders (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Plenary Symposium Speakers, 1973; 3 folders (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Press Information, 1973; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Program, 1973; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Program - Committee on Genetics & Society, 1973 (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Program - Exhibits & Demos., 1973; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Program - General Correspondence, 1973 (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Program Committee - Cancelled Programs, 1973 (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Program Committee - Davis Day, 1973 (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Program Committee - Gen. Correspondence, 1973; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Program Committee - International Fed. of Genetics Meeting, 1973; 4 folders (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Program Committee - Invitations, 1973; 4 folders (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Program Committee - Isozyme Conference, 1973 (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Program Committee - Minutes, 1973 (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics. Program Committee - Welcoming Session, 1973 (Box 33)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Publications, 1973; 7 folders (Box 34)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Registration, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Africa, Asia, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Belgium, Canada, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Cancer Institutes, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Commerical Companies, 1973 (Box 34)
        - France, 1973 (Box 34)
        - General, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Germany, 1973; 2 folders (Box 34)
        - Government, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Great Britain, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Hungary, India, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Iran, Israel, Italy, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Japan, Korea, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Laboratories, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Medical Schools/Hospitals, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Mexico, Netherlands, 1973 (Box 34)
        - New Zealand, Norway, Scotland, 1973 (Box 34)
        - South Africa, South America, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Spain, Sweden, Switzerland, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Universities, 1973; 2 folders (Box 34)
        - USSR, Yugoslavia, 1973 (Box 34)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Special Advisory Committee, 1973; 3 folders (Box 34)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Symposium, 1973; 9 folders (Box 34)
        - Animal Genetics, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Behavior Genetics, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Developmental Genetics, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Evolution, 1973 (Box 34)
        - Gene & Chromosome Inactivatior, 1973 (Box 35)
        - Genetic Exchange, 1973 (Box 35)
        - Genetic Repair, 1973 (Box 35)
        - Genetics of Disease in Plants and Animals, 1973 (Box 35)
        - Immuno Genetics, 1973 (Box 35)
        - Meiosis, 1973 (Box 35)
        - Mutagenesis, 1973 (Box 35)
        - Non-chromosomal Inheritance, 1973 (Box 35)
        - Origin of Cultivated Plants, 1973 (Box 35)
        - Population Genetics, 1973 (Box 35)
        - Radiation Genetics, 1973 (Box 35)
        - Somatic Cell Genetics, 1973 (Box 35)
        - Teaching of Genetics, 1973 (Box 35)
        - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Symposium Speakers, 1973; 12 folders (Box 35)
        - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Symposium Speakers - U.S.A., 1973; 4 folders (Box 35)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Travel Awards (folders 1-3), 1973; 3 folders (Box 35)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Travel Awards (folders 4-27), 1973; 23 folders (Box 36)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - Travel Awards - Rejections, 1973; 5 folders (Box 36)
      - XIII International Congress of Genetics - University Facilities, 1973; 3 folders (Box 36)
  - Records, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
    - Committee on Genetics, Race, Intelligence, 1974-1975; 0.5 Linear feet
      Behavioral genetics, IQ; Committee activities; Genetics Society of America; Human genetics -- Race; Jensen, Arthur Robert; Shockley, William
      - Committee on Genetics, Race, Intelligence - Background Material, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
      - Committee on Genetics, Race, Intelligence - Committee Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Crow, James F x Elizabeth Russell, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Echols, Harrison X Elizabeth Russell, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Green, M. M., 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Nance, Walter E, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Perkins, David x Elizabeth Russell, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Prakash, Satya x Elizabeth Russell, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Russell, Elizabeth x Baer, Dee. Analysis of data., 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Smithies, Oliver x Elizabeth Russell, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Spofford, Janice B x Elizabeth Russell, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Turner, John R G, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
      - Committee on Genetics, Race, Intelligence - Correspondence, General, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Altman, Sidney, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Anderson, V Elving, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Atkins, Charles, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Band, Henretta Trent, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Beadle, George, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Becker, Walter A, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Bennett, Jack, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Bertani, G, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Bishop, Jack B, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Bodmer, Walter F, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Bradford, Eric G, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Bradley, B P, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Brenner, Sydney, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Bruck, David L, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Burdick, Allan B, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Caspari, Ernst, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Cook, Robert, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Corcos, Alain, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Crenshaw, John W, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Crow, James F, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Davis, Bernard D x "Novel Pressures on Advance of Sci.', 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - DeFries, J C, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Dempster, Everett R, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Dirks, V A, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Ehrman, Lee, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Falkinham, Joseph O, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Farmer, James L, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Forest, Charlene L, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Fowler, Robert G, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Fox, Allen S, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Frankel, Anne W K, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Franklin, Naomi C, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Frost, Justin N, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Fuller, John L, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Futuyma, Douglas J, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Gall, Graham A E, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Glass, Bentley, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Grahn, Douglas, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Green, Earl L, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Green, M' M, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Gregg, Thomas G, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Gross, Sheila, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Hayne, E G, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Hirsch, Jerry, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Horowitz, N H, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Hungate, Frank B, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Irwin, Robert, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Janick, Jules, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Judd, Burke H, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Kempthorne, Oscar, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Kidd, Kenneth K, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - King, Charles E, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - King, James C, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - King, Jonathan, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Klein, Thomas W, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Kunicki-Goldfinger, W, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Lacks, Sanford, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Landman, Otto E, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Lappé, Marc, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Lawrence, Patricia S, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Lederberg, Joshua, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Lewis, E B, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Lewontin, Richard C, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Libby, William J, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Lieb, Margaret, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Lindsley, Dan L, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Lippincott, William H, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Loehlin, John C, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Lynch, Carol B, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Magill, Clint W, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Margulis, L, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Mauer, Irving, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - McKenzie, Wendell H, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Melechen, Norman E, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Milkman, Roger, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Moore, John A, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Morton, Newton E, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Nanney, David L, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Novick, Richard, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Opitz, John M, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Pearson, Helen M, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Perkins, David, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Pollitzer, William S, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Prakash, Satya, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Preer, John R, Jr., 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Radin, David N, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Rasmusen, Benjamin A, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Reed, Edward, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Remondini, David J, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Ringo, John M, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Runner, Meredith N, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Scandalios, John G, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Schell, Stephen C, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Schwinck, Ilse, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Scott, J P, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Sears, E R, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Seecof, Robert, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Shaw, Margery W, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Sheridan, William & Euger Soares, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Siciliano, Michael J, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Smith, Benjamin W, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Smith, H H, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Smithies, Oliver, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Smouse, Peter E, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Sonneborn, Tracy M, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Spielman, Richard, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Spiess, Eliot B, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Stadler, David, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Stebbins, G Ledyard S, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Stern, Curt, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Stone, Bill, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Susman, Millard, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Sutton, Eldon, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Suzuki, David T, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Tessman, Irwin, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Thomas, Charles A, Jr., 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Torris, Andrew M, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Turner, John R G, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Walker, George W R, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Wallace, Bruce, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Wilson, Allan C, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Wilson, Stanley P, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Winkle-Swift, Karen Van, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Witkin, Evelyn M, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
        - Wright, Sewall, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
      - Committee on Genetics, Race, Intelligence - Draft Resolutions, 1974-1975; 2 folders (Box 37)
      - Committee on Genetics, Race, Intelligence - Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
    - Genetics Society of America - Membership File. A-E, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
    - Genetics Society of America - Membership File. F-L, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
    - Genetics Society of America - Membership File. M-R, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
    - Genetics Society of America - Membership File. S-Z, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
  - Committee on Historical Documents, 1978-1984; 2.0 Linear feet
    Committee activities; Genetics Society of America; History of biology, especially genetics; Preservation of historical materials